Hong Kong is asleep.
There are no pedestrians, no cars,
no movement.
This remote street still has many young
voices.
They have never been educated,
they have no family warmth, and no one to
guide them on the right path.
So, under the influence of the devil,
they fell into the abyss of sin.
The black area is where they live.
Cruel struggle is the condition for their
survival.
Now, the story begins.
Let's go!
That voice is the cry of the wind.
That voice is the softness of the night.
Do you know where it comes from?
Do you know who it belongs to?
It can't see the life in the abyss.
It can't hear the voice in the window.
It only sees broken hearts and tears.
It can't see the life in the abyss.
It can't hear the voice in the window.
It only sees broken hearts and tears.
That voice is the softness of the night.
Do you know where it comes from?
Do you know who it belongs to?
It can't see the voice in the window.
Brother, we'll beat them up tonight.
They won't fall for our trap.
They thought they could get Lisa,
but they didn't expect to get the mute.
The mute is really something.
Guess what those losers are doing now?
It hurts so much.
Brother, don't be angry.
Don't be angry?
They didn't find the mute, but you all got
hurt like this.
What are you talking about?
Where did the mute come from?
I don't know.
He's really good at martial arts.
I think we should bring Zhou Zhiqiang
along.
Zhou Zhiqiang?
Can he do it?
Him?
Zhou Zhiqiang.
Well done.
Little tiger, did I say anything wrong?
Zhou, did he call you?
What are you doing?
My men don't believe in your martial arts.
I asked them to taste your martial arts.
Luckily, you didn't embarrass yourself.
Look at that.
Bastard.
Zhou.
I'm not here to fight.
I'm here to...
To fight, right?
There's a mute.
He's tall and good at martial arts.
We are no match for him.
So I...
Zhou.
You know I want Andy.
How can you go out and make trouble again?
I'll just kill him.
Gu.
Don't talk nonsense.
Tonight at nine o'clock, I'll be waiting
for you at the Lu Tian restaurant in the
suburb.
Let's have a beer.
What are you doing?
Mali, are you happy?
Yes.
Brother, thank you for the treat.
You're 21 years old this year,
you know?
I'm very happy.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I hope we'll get married next year.
Brother, it's not safe to go out.
These rascals are here too.
Let's go somewhere else.
Wait a minute.
Brother, where are we going to work?
It would be a shame if we quit.
And we also invited Zhou Zhiqiang to come
here.
Sit down.
Come on.
Hey, boy.
Come on home, baby.
You know I need you.
Hey, come on home.
Do they want to tear down our stage?
Kill them.
Don't move.
Way down in Louisiana Today is my
daughter's birthday.
I want her to be happy.
I don't want her to be shocked.
That's right.
I don't want Zhenni to see our ugliness.
I'll tell her right away.
Listen to me.
You can't go out tonight.
Don't let my Zhenni be shocked.
Do you understand?
I can't feel the time to change your love.
Hey, Zhou Zhiqiang is here.
Everything is so pathetic now.
Xiao Zhou.
Come on.
Sit down.
It seems to be very lively.
It's a coincidence.
I'll tell you later.
Sit down and have a drink.
Why don't you drink?
Xiao Zhou.
Buy some cigarettes.
Let's go over there.
Xiao Zhou.
Didn't you go to buy cigarettes?
I didn't buy it.
When he sees a woman, he forgets
everything.
Listen.
It's time to dance.
When the lights go out, we'll dance in the
dark.
Let's see if you have the luck to find
your beloved girl.
Let's go.
I know.
Today is your birthday.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
My name is Zhou Zhiqiang.
I work at a gas station nearby.
What kind of job?
I'm a bus driver.
Sometimes I repair machines under the bus.
Yongzhuo went to buy cigarettes again.
I think he must have gone to the swimming
pool.
This guy is so handsome.
That's good.
Let him seduce their Miss Hong.
I know where you live.
You know that street well.
There's a small alley behind.
There's a construction site next to it.
You can see the balcony behind your house
from the alley.
You're so stupid.
That guy is Gu Xiong's man.
He...
Don't touch him.
Jenny, sing a love song.
I don't know how to sing.
Come on.
No.
I know what you're thinking.
After you danced with that guy...
Don't talk to me.
I'm not talking to you.
I don't want to listen.
I want to talk.
Stop it.
You're so annoying.
But that guy asked you to dance.
It's a conspiracy.
Didn't I warn you just now?
He's Gu Xiong's man.
Boss, I'll talk to him.
Jenny.
We did some research just now.
That guy is suspicious.
Listen.
You're my sister.
You have to listen to me.
How dare you.
As long as I can find you, I don't care
about anything else.
But...
Your friend is my brother's sworn enemy.
I'm not.
He doesn't allow me to talk to you.
You can explain to him.
You went on a date with Gu Xiong tonight.
It was just a drink.
I won't listen to him.
Jenny, I won't help him fight with him.
Shh.
Don't be so loud.
How do you know a guy like Gu Xiong?
I'm not a good guy either.
I met him at the nursing home.
At that time, the nursing home was very
strict.
So we ran away.
No home.
No family.
We wandered the streets all day.
Then...
we did illegal things.
Until one day, I accidentally killed
someone during a robbery.
As a result, I was sentenced to three
years in prison.
Three years later, as soon as I got out of
prison, I swore to myself that I would
start over.
So I found my current job.
Now I have a job and a life.
I feel safe around me.
You don't hate me, do you?
You are very honest.
If only my brother was as wise as you.
That would be great.
But he...
Hey, hurry up.
Let's find a way to influence them.
My brother?
Gu Xiong?
Tell them to find a decent job.
Us?
Can we?
You think you can't?
I...
Zhen Ni, be brave.
I'll help you.
You help me.
I'm going down.
Zhen Ni!
Come out!
Zhen Ni.
I'm scared.
I've never had a girlfriend.
I met you tonight.
They are looking for me.
I like you.
What about you?
They will find me.
Tell me.
Do you like me?
Zhixian.
The company closes in half an hour.
Go back and see what's going on.
Zhen Ni!
Are you ready?
What is it?
They are leaving.
So be it.
Don't be upset.
It's your birthday today.
They are all guests.
We are leaving.
Bye.
Zhen Ni, I'll come to see you after work
tomorrow.
Let's go shopping together.
Okay.
I'll walk you down.
I'll find...
I know.
Please come in.
Please.
Don't shout.
I'll call her right away.
Please.
This way.
You...
What do you want me to do?
I want you to take it off.
Take it off?
Fei Fei, let me do it.
Okay.
You...
Don't go.
You got it wrong.
I'm not here to see you.
What?
My clothes are taken off.
You want to take it off?
No way.
Don't run.
Don't want to take it off.
What is it?
Get out of the way.
Shen Qiang, come with me.
Brother.
You promised to help me.
Guo Xiao.
What's the point of living in this place?
You gave your youth to a drug dealer.
What else do you want?
I didn't expect you to not only refuse to
help me, but also to teach me a lesson.
Stop fighting with Zhang Jinming right
now.
I can't.
You shouldn't have a grudge against him.
This grudge is deeper than the sea.
Why?
What do you know?
Let me tell you.
He grabbed my guest.
He grabbed my Miss Hong.
This is not stealing my job.
This is killing me.
This guy is a real bastard.
Guo Xiao.
Don't persuade me.
Boss, come out.
Wait for me.
Don't go.
Boss.
I overheard your conversation just now.
Yes.
I almost got mad at him.
Don't get mad.
Boss's advice.
If you make a mistake, you make a mistake.
Use Zhou's relationship with Zhang
Jinming's sister to bring his sister to
our doorstep.
This can not only make money, but also
avenge Zhang Jinming.
At that time, I'm afraid that Zhou won't
come to us.
That's great.
Think about it right now.
Remember, don't act rashly.
I'm leaving.
Wait a minute.
No wonder you came to persuade me.
Because you have fallen in love with Zhang
Jinming's sister.
So what?
If so, of course I should help you.
And I shouldn't hate Zhang Jinming so
much.
And?
Brother, tell me.
For you and his sister.
All right, all right.
You guys get off work early.
Let me do this.
You're usually the laziest.
Why did you change your mind today?
I think there must be something strange.
Don't talk nonsense.
Jenny.
Let's go first.
You're early.
I'm in a hurry to see you.
How long have they been here?
One day they will know.
I'm going to pack up.
Let me help you.
Okay.
I have good news for you.
I have persuaded Gu Xiong.
Really?
He promised me not to worry about your
brother anymore.
And...
find a proper job.
Will he really listen to you?
If our plan succeeds, how will you repay
me?
I don't know.
Let me make a condition, okay?
Marry me.
We guessed it right.
That guy named Zhou is deliberately
seducing Jenny.
Yes.
He appeared on Jenny's birthday night.
He is Gu Xiong's mastermind.
I think this conspiracy is not simple.
This guy.
Let me deal with him.
You have a chance to revenge.
Don't send it.
I don't want to show it to my brother.
I'll come to you on time tomorrow after
work.
Don't be late.
I won't fight with you.
But I won't let you go.
There's nothing between you and me.
If you dare to touch my girlfriend,
I'll give you a hard time.
Go.
Boy, this is a lesson for you.
If you do it again, I'll teach you a
lesson next time.
She is mine.
If she is disloyal to me, I'll destroy
her.
Go.
You've changed.
You don't listen to my advice.
You don't listen to my words.
I'm your brother.
I'm your only family.
You won't deny it, will you?
When I scolded Lin Si, she told me over
and over again to take good care of you.
Take care of you.
Don't follow her old ways.
Today, I'm trying to make a living out of
a crime.
But I've never let you get a little bit of
a crime on me.
Now, you're in love with my enemy's
friend, a man who is a hooligan.
I...
I'm disappointed in you.
I'm heartbroken.
That's why I should love a man who is a
hooligan like you.
I won't let you marry him.
You've been trying to get him to marry me.
You don't know my intentions.
You're making excuses.
I'm using him.
Do you know he is my only master?
I'm going to catch him.
Stop arguing.
You can't deny your brother's love for
you.
Jenny, you should listen to him.
I won't listen to him I'm glad I didn't go
to work tonight.
Otherwise, you'd have to go to the
hospital.
Thank you, Shirley.
You were beaten like this.
Why don't you call the police?
Yes, I'll call the police for you.
No, no, don't.
What a fool.
I know.
I don't know what he's afraid of.
Nothing.
Because it's a misunderstanding.
He hasn't come these days?
No phone calls?
No.
Listen to me.
Don't trust boys too much.
I know.
If he doesn't come to you, don't go to
him.
But I have to go to him once.
I didn't want to come to you again.
But I want to tell you one last thing.
You are a heartless person.
Everything you said was a lie.
Your attitude is no different from those
people.
Don't think that because you don't come to
me, I'll be angry.
I'm telling you, I won't.
I'll never...
You misunderstood him.
After he sent you home that night,
he was beaten up by your brother's men.
Then he warned you not to be with him.
Otherwise, it would be bad for you.
So, for your safety, he didn't dare to go
to you again.
Now you understand everything,
right?
Zhiqiang!
Zhen Ni!
Don't worry.
I will change Gu Xiong.
You don't hate my brother?
In order to achieve our goal, I will try
my best.
Thank you, Zhiqiang.
How old are you?
Seventeen.
Very suitable.
What do I do for a living?
Very simple.
In that little room.
What do you do in that little room?
Go and take a look.
How much is it a month?
Don't say three thousand.
If you become famous, six thousand is not
worth it.
Six thousand?
If you have money, you can buy new clothes
like Miss Qian Jin, wear high heels,
use French perfume, live in a foreign
house, and drive a private car.
Listen to me, I will teach you how to deal
with guests.
If you do it well, I'm sure you'll be
famous in a month.
Do you understand?
Our business is getting better these days.
I heard that girl is very good.
She looks like a mischievous girl.
She ran away from home last month.
Jianmin.
Yes.
Do you have a way?
Wait for you.
Jianmin.
Do you know any girls?
Yes.
Miss Xin.
Shasha.
She has a lot of workers.
These guests are waiting for her.
I'll bring it as soon as possible.
Don't take it off.
I want to talk to you first.
Shasha.
She's sitting on the stage.
Please sit for a while.
Sit inside.
As long as you're willing, I'll double the
price.
What about Mr. Zhao?
Don't worry about him.
You're not selling it to them anyway.
How is it?
I'm afraid they'll beat me.
Don't worry.
We have more people fighting than them.
I'll order it for you first.
Miss Lulu has a lot of guests.
Why don't you do something else?
We like her.
She came to your house, so we followed her
here.
I know.
Please sit for a while.
I'll bring it to you as soon as she comes
out.
Okay.
Lulu.
Wait a minute.
You're here.
You're Shasha.
This is Lulu.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Wait a minute.
I'll be right back.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
We've found out that their Lulu is our
Shasha.
That's outrageous.
Gu Xiong.
Yes.
Shasha is our money tree.
We have to get her back.
Otherwise, don't come back to see me.
Yes.
Do it right now.
What a joke.
The little girl you introduced to me just
now has been taken away again.
I didn't take her away.
Then why did she have to leave?
How do we know?
It's none of my business.
Say it.
Whichever family gives more money,
just do it there.
Do you understand the rules of the trade?
Do you want another top guy?
He lives in the apartment.
We'll let him go when we've had enough.
What do you think?
You little bastard.
Go, go, go.
Damn it.
Go.
Hello.
Gu Xiong.
Are you free today?
I want to meet you.
I'm not free today.
I have a holiday tomorrow.
But I have a date with Jenny.
That's even better.
Xiao Zhou.
Ever since you met Jenny, I haven't
invited you yet.
So...
All right, all right.
I'm busy.
See you in the old place tomorrow.
Goodbye.
You're welcome, Miss Zhang.
Xiao Zhou is my brother.
You're not strangers, of course.
I heard about your relationship from
Zhiqiang.
He's been with me since I was a kid.
He eats when he's hungry.
He talks when he's rich.
That's right.
Now...
he's a decent man.
I'm a big brother.
But...
I'm still wandering in the dark.
Then why don't you learn from him?
Learn from him?
Yes, learn from him.
From now on, I must find a right path.
Brother.
Thank you for your encouragement.
Come on, have a drink.
Have you been to the clothing store to see
him?
Today is the holiday of the clothing
store.
There's no one there.
Where did he go?
How would I know?
Damn it.
He's still with that kid.
My brother...
is the best at taking pictures.
Come on.
Take a picture for Miss Zhang.
Xiao Zhou, come here.
Okay.
Brother.
Look.
Damn it.
It's on the billboard at the door.
It's your sister's picture.
Her name is Li Li.
Damn it.
I'm going to smash his place.
Don't move.
How dare you!
How dare you set up a trap for Qing Zhou.
You betrayed him.
What are you talking about?
Let go of me.
You let them take advantage of me.
You let them take revenge on me.
You totally humiliated me.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you.
You are not allowed to be with Qing Zhou.
If I see you again, I'm going to beat you
to death.
Listen to me.
I have nothing to say.
It's all a fact.
What's there to explain?
I won't listen.
You are not allowed to be with Qing Zhou.
Do you hear me?
Jin
Mi.
Come here.
Don't be sad, Zhen Ni.
You can stay at my house for now.
How can your brother be so unreasonable?
He beat my sister.
I've never seen such a man.
I'll go to him right now.
Ask him why he beat you.
Don't go.
I'm not afraid of him.
You want to make trouble again?
You promised me you wouldn't fight again.
Did you forget?
If I don't look for him, he will look for
me.
Is my sister here?
No.
Where is she?
She hasn't come to work for a few days.
What?
She hasn't come to work for a few days?
Yes.
Do you know where she is?
I'm sorry, I don't know either.
Okay, let's go.
Which lady do you like?
Is there a new lady here?
Her name is Li Li.
Yes.
Please go inside.
I'll call her right away.
Let's go.
My guess is right.
These two guys are really here.
Okay.
This is my business.
I'll take care of it.
Jianmin, you can't go alone.
Don't stop me.
There is a tiger on the mountain.
The direction is to the tiger's mountain.
Don't move.
Get out of my way.
What can I do for you?
I'm here to get some advice.
Is it because of what happened to Zhang's
brother?
No, it's a private matter.
It's about my sister's disappearance.
This is a private matter.
We'd better talk outside.
What time and place?
Anywhere.
At 12 o'clock in the evening, at the
restaurant in the suburb.
Sit down.
Mr. Zhang, what can I do for you?
Mr. Zhang.
You are too good.
If you dare to hurt him, I'll kill you.
If you don't hand him over soon,
I'll die with you at any cost.
Do you hear me?
Mr. Zhang, please.
So what do we do now?
As long as you hand over my sister,
you can do whatever you want.
Why don't you hand over Lulu to our
company?
In addition, I'll pay you 10,000 yuan as a
loss.
What do you say?
When do we make the deal?
Anytime.
At 10 o'clock in the evening, in the
suburb.
It's a deal.
10 o
'clock.
Zhao, if you have enough friends,
hand over Zhang's sister right away.
What do you say?
Mr. Gu, I really despise you.
What do you think?
Not only are you not kind, but you are
also very strict.
What do you mean?
Aren't you using Zhengyi as a sacrifice
now?
I won't bother you.
Are you making clothes?
No.
I want to know where Zhengyi is.
We don't know.
You must know.
Please inform him right away.
Call me before 10 o'clock tonight.
Remember, don't make a mistake.
Let's go.
Zhengyi, Mr. Gu just came to the store to
see you.
He came to see me?
He asked you to call him before 10 o
'clock.
Something must have happened.
Why did he come to see me?
Mr. Gu went to see you, so I guess Zhengyi
is with you.
Don't worry about me.
If I can't find you tonight, many people
will die.
It has nothing to do with me if you want
to fight or kill.
It has something to do with you.
I don't care.
You can't leave me alone.
Zhengyi, you shouldn't hate your brother.
You shouldn't run away from home.
He can't hide it from you.
No, he cares about you.
He cares about your reputation and future.
Do you know?
That guy named Gu is framing you.
He took your photo and made him deal with
your brother's conspiracy.
He reported your photo and hung it at the
door of Jiulian.
He called you the new Jiulian girl.
I don't think Zhengyi will call us.
If he doesn't come now, we will be
embarrassed.
Gu took advantage of you and framed your
brother.
And he made the situation worse.
I'm going to find Gu.
No, don't go.
Why are you stopping me?
It's no use.
I will solve this problem.
Is Gu here?
They just left.
They must have gone to the drying plant.
I'll go to the guardhouse.
Mary, go home with Zhengyi first.
Zhengyi, as long as I'm there,
everything will be clear.
From now on, your brother will know us.
Brother Gu, I brought the money and people
you asked for.
What about our brother Zhang's sister
Zhengyi?
Oh, this thing.
Brother Zhang's sister is not feeling
well.
She is resting in a place.
I will send her back in three days.
What did you say?
Say that again.
Don't be so impatient.
We are just out for a walk.
Three days.
Three days?
You never keep your word.
Get down.
Don't hit him.
Listen to me.
Stop.
You shouldn't hit him.
Don't hit him.
You should have killed him.
You shouldn't have killed him.
Let him go.
You murderer.
You should have listened to me.
You shouldn't have killed him.
Go.
Don't move.
Get in the car.
Zhengyi.
If only this wish could come true.
How beautiful, how happy.
And how free and comfortable.
Mary.
At that time, you married my brother.
I married Zhiqiang.
We got married.
We had a good job.
We lived together.
Mary.
Don't you want to live like this?
At that time, my brother was no longer
used by villains.
He could raise his head and be a man.
Be a real man.
I'm afraid your brother will not be able
to enjoy those days.
Shaofu.
What happened?
Jieming...
He was stabbed.
What did you say?
That heartless Gu Xiong.
He really did it?
That heartless man is not Gu Xiong.
It's Zhu Zhiqiang.
Zhu Zhiqiang.
No.
It can't be.
Zhiqiang, it can't be.
You...
You're lying.
I'm not lying.
It's Zhu Zhiqiang.
Zhu Zhiqiang.
Mary.
If my husband dies, you can't live.
Come with me.
Mary is right.
If there's anything wrong with Jieming,
it's a murder.
You...
Why did you kill my brother?
Why are you so heartless?
Mary, listen to me.
You said you were a guard.
You said you stopped them from fighting.
You lied to me.
I'm not lying.
You hurt my brother.
Listen to me.
You're lying.
Listen to me, okay?
You did everything to me.
Yinglan.
You're not human.
You're a murderer.
Listen to me.
I rushed to the scene.
They were fighting.
I rushed in front of them.
I stopped them from fighting.
But they were almost crazy.
They couldn't hear me.
I rushed over in a panic.
I caught Gu Xiong.
I told him about our plot.
Just then, your brother stabbed him.
I blamed your brother for not killing him.
But they wouldn't let me go.
In the end, your brother rushed over and
stabbed me.
I didn't kill him on purpose.
He rushed over.
Do you understand?
What should we do?
Zhiqiang, what should we do now?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
Zhiqiang.
Zhenning, do you hate me?
Will you ignore me from now on?
No, I won't.
I won't.
Zhenning.
I'll go buy some painkillers.
I'll go with you.
Zhenning.
Hello.
Okay.
I'll be right there.
My brother is bleeding.
They wouldn't dare to send your brother to
the hospital.
Yes.
What should we do now?
Go see him now.
I'll go find the nurse in the same room.
Zhenning, do me a favor.
What is it?
Go save a person.
No.
But...
I won't blame Zhiqiang.
I won't blame anyone.
I deserve it.
I deserve my retribution.
Zhenning, calm down.
Zhiqiang has gone to see the nurse.
You son of a bitch.
Just as we expected.
Are you really going to save Zhang
Jianmin?
Our brother just died under his knife.
You are not only not worried, but you are
going to save him.
Do you have the courage?
I don't have time to waste with you.
Let's go.
Stop.
It's not that easy.
I'm telling you.
Don't think we don't know.
Brother Gu's death is a conspiracy between
you and Zhang Jianmin.
Now I want you to pay with your life.
Go.
Xiaolian, Xiao Huo is hiding in the dark.
You go alone.
Don't blame me.
I told you, murderers pay with their
lives.
Xiao Huo, don't kill him.
I beg you, don't kill him.
Xiao Huo.
Don't go.
He can't live.
Stop.
Zhiqiang.
Xiaolian.
Zhiqiang, I rushed to the warehouse.
Zhang Jianmin is dead.
Go.
Shaofu is biting you with a gun.
Where is Zhen Ni?
He chased after him to stop Shaofu.
But Ma Li is going to kill him.
Zhen Ni.
Zhiqiang.
Zhiqiang Zhen Ni.
Zhen Ni,
Zhen Ni.
Zhiqiang.
So the devil's temptation will not stop.
Can you get rid of his temptation?
Can you see what is the path of light?
What is the evil trap?
This story is a mirror of reality.